<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="quote_bodies">
        <item>Dont spur a willing horse</item>
        <item>Men are more accountable for their motives, than for anything else; and primarily, morality consists in the motives, that is in the affections.</item>
        <item>Aerodynamically, the bumble bee shouldnt be able to fly, but the bumble bee doesnt know it so it goes on flying anyway.</item>
        <item>God made man to go by motives, and he will not go without them, any more than a boat without steam or a balloon without gas.</item>
        <item>You cannot raise a man up by calling him down.</item>
        <item>There are two levers for moving men -- interest and fear. </item>
        <item>Striving for excellence motivates you; striving for perfection is demoralizing. </item>
        <item>Life takes on meaning when you become motivated, set goals and charge after them in an unstoppable manner. </item>
        <!--ALONE -->
        <item>Hasty climbers have sudden falls. </item>
        <item>We are told never to cross a bridge until we come to it, but this world is owned by men who have crossed bridges in their imagination far ahead of the crowd. </item>
        <item>When ambition ends, happiness begins. </item>
        <item>Children, you must remember something. A man without ambition is dead. A man with ambition but no love is dead. A man with ambition and love for his blessings here on earth is ever so alive. </item>
        <item>Very few people are ambitious in the sense of having a specific image of what they want to achieve. Most peoples sights are only toward the next run, the next increment of money. </item>
        <item>Ambition -- it is the last infirmity of noble minds. </item>
        <item>All ambitions are lawful except those that climb upward on the miseries or credulities of mankind. </item>
        <item>Ambition. An overmastering desire to be vilified by enemies while living and made ridiculous by friends when dead. </item>
        <item>No bird soars too high if he soars with his own wings. </item>
        <item>Great ambition is the passion of a great character. Those endowed with it may perform very good or very bad acts. All depends on the principals which direct them. </item>
        <item>Shoot for the moon. Even if you miss, youll land among the stars. </item>
        <item>What I aspired to be and was not, comforts me. </item>
        <item>Tis not what man does which exalts him, but what man Would do! </item>
        <item>Ambition is not what man does... but what man would do. </item>
        <item>There are only two ways of getting on in the world: by ones own industry, or by the stupidity of others. </item>
        <item>The slave has but one master, the ambitious man has as many as there are persons whose aid may contribute to the advancement of his fortunes. </item>
        <item>Ambition can creep as well as soar. </item>
        <item>Like dogs in a wheel, birds in a cage, or squirrels in a chain, ambitious men still climb and climb, with great labor, and incessant anxiety, but never reach the top. </item>
        <item>He who surpasses or subdues mankind, must look down on the hate of those below. </item>
        <item>As falls the dew on quenchless sands, blood only serves to wash ambitions hands. </item>
        <item>The men who succeed are the efficient few. They are the few who have the ambition and will power to develop themselves. </item>
        <item>It is commonly supposed that the art of pleasing is a wonderful aid in the pursuit of fortune; but the art of being bored is infinitely more successful. </item>
        <item>Big results require big ambitions. </item>
        <item>When you are aspiring to the highest place, it is honorable to reach the second or even the third rank. </item>
        <!--ANGRY-->
        <item>	If you are patient in one moment of anger, you will escape a hundred days of sorrow. </item>
        <item>Anger is not only inevitable, but it is necessary. For in its place is indifference, the worst of all human qualities. </item>
        <item>He who is slow to anger has great understanding, but he who has a hasty temper exalts folly. </item>
        <item>There are two things a person should never be angry at, what they can help, and what they cannot. </item>
        <item>No one is as angry as the person who is wrong. </item>
        <item>The wrath of brothers is fierce and devilish. </item>
        <item>Anger is as a stone cast into a wasps nest. </item>
        <item>Indulge not thyself in the passion of anger; it is whetting a sword to wound thine own breast, or murder thy friend. </item>
        <item>As the whirlwind in its fury teareth up trees, and deformeth the face of nature, or as an earthquake in its convulsions overturneth whole cities; so the rage of an angry man throweth mischief around him. </item>
        <item>Holding anger is a poison. It eats you from inside. We think that hating is a weapon that attacks the person who harmed us. But hatred is a curved blade. And the harms we do, we do to ourselves. Mitch Albom</item>
        <item>It takes two flints to make a fire. </item>
        <item>I used to store my anger and it affected my play. Now I get it out. Im never rude to my playing partner. Im very focused on the ball. Then its over. </item>
        <item>Men often make up in wrath what they want in reason. </item>
        <item>I love to see a young girl go out and grab the world by the lapels. Lifes a bitch. Youve got to go out and kick ass. </item>
        <item>Bitterness is like cancer. It eats upon the host. But anger is like fire. It burns it all clean. </item>
        <item>Consider how much more you often suffer from your anger and grief, than from those very things for which you are angry and grieved. </item>
        <item>Angry men are blind and foolish, for reason at such a time takes flight and, in her absence, wrath plunders all the riches of the intellect, while the judgment remains the prisoner of its own pride. </item>
        <item>Anger is always concerned with individuals, whereas hatred is directed also against classes: we all hate any thief and any informer. Moreover, anger can be cured by time; but hatred cannot. The one aims at giving pain to its object, the other at doing him harm; the angry man wants his victim to feel; the hater does not mind whether they feel or not. </item>
        <item>Anyone can become angry - that is easy. But to be angry with the right person, to the right degree, at the right time, for the right purpose, and in the right way; this is not easy. </item>
        <item>We praise a man who feels angry on the right grounds and against the right persons and also in the right manner at the right moment and for the right length of time. </item>
        <item>When thou art above measure angry, bethink thee how momentary is mans life. </item>
        <item>How much more grievous are the consequences of anger than the causes of it. </item>
        <item>Anger cannot be dishonest. </item>
        <item>Anger makes dull men witty but it keeps them poor. </item>
        <item>Rage cannot be hidden, it can only be dissembled. This dissembling deludes the thoughtless, and strengthens rage and adds, to rage, contempt. </item>
        <!--<Architecture>-->
        <item>A structure becomes architectural, and not sculptural, when its elements no longer have their justification in nature. </item>
        <item>In my experience, if you have to keep the lavatory door shut by extending your left leg, its modern architecture. </item>
        <item>When it comes to getting things done, we need fewer architects and more bricklayers. </item>
        <item>Where do architects and designers get their ideas? The answer, of course, is mainly from other architects and designers, so is it mere casuistry to distinguish between tradition and plagiarism? </item>
        <item>Architect. One who drafts a plan of your house, and plans a draft of your money. </item>
        <item>Architecture is inhabited sculpture. </item>
        <item>You have to give this much to the Luftwaffe: when it knocked down our buildings it did not replace them with anything more offensive than rubble. We did that. </item>
        <item>All architecture is great architecture after sunset; perhaps architecture is really a nocturnal art, like the art of fireworks. </item>
        <item>A building is akin to dogma; it is insolent, like dogma. Whether or no it is permanent, it claims permanence, like a dogma. People ask why we have no typical architecture of the modern world, like impressionism in painting. Surely it is obviously because we have not enough dogmas; we cannot bear to see anything in the sky that is solid and enduring, anything in the sky that does not change like the clouds of the sky. </item>
        <item>The principle of the Gothic architecture is infinity made imaginable. </item>
        <item>In short, the building becomes a theatrical demonstration of its functional ideal. In this romanticism, high-tech architecture is, of course, no different in spirit -- if totally different in form -- from all the romantic architecture of the past. </item>
        <item>The terrifying and edible beauty of Art Nouveau architecture. </item>
        <item>The job of buildings is to improve human relations: architecture must ease them, not make them worse. </item>
        <item>A bold architectural statement turns a public building into a landmark, but it is in the details where the architect becomes the real storyteller. </item>
        <item>People actually ask me why I bring in projects on budget and on time. It seems I am not living up to the fashionable genius role. I really enjoy when a project gets down to the wire, and through sheer force of will and faith in our process, we cross the goal line, when most people thought it impossible. </item>
        <item>There are many satisfactions in public architecture but one of the greatest is the moment when you unveil a project and suddenly a group of adults </item>
        <item>Some architects have a preconceived notion of what a building should be </item>
        <item>It takes a great client to create great architecture. </item>
        <item>Our work is really about taking the best of what is in a place and working that into a project. Wed like to take your vision and goals and weave that into all the bricks and mortar and steel and glass put together, along with all the functional things that we need to make the airport work better. </item>
        <item>Dont fight forces, use them. </item>
        <item>Light, Gods eldest daughter, is a principal beauty in a building. </item>
        <item>A modern, harmonic and lively architecture is the visible sign of an authentic democracy. </item>
        <item>Architects, painters, and sculptors must recognize anew and learn to grasp the composite character of a building both as an entity and in its separate parts. Only then will their work be imbued with the architectonic spirit which it has lost as salon art. Together let us desire, conceive, and create the new structure of the future, which will embrace architecture and sculpture and painting in one unity and which will one day rise toward heaven from the hands of a million workers like the crystal symbol of a new faith. </item>
        <item>The only legitimate artists in England are the architects. </item>
        <item>Architecture is to make us know and remember who we are. </item>
        <!--ART-->
        <item>Art is permitted to survive only if it renounces the right to be different, and integrates itself into the omnipotent realm of the profane. </item>
        <item> Art is an experience, not the formulation of a problem. </item>
        <item> Artists are, above all, men who want to become inhuman. </item>
        <item> Without poets, without artists, men would soon weary of nature s monotony. The sublime idea men have of the universe would collapse with dizzying speed. The order which we find in nature, and which is only an effect of art, would at once vanish. Everything would break up in chaos. There would be no seasons, no civilization, no thought, no humanity; even life would give way, and the impotent void would reign everywhere. </item>
        <item> Now the work of art also represents a state of final equilibrium, of accomplished order and maximum relative entropy, and there are those who resent it. But art is not meant to stop the stream of life. Within a narrow span of duration and space the work of art concentrates a view of the human condition; and sometimes it marks the steps of progression, just as a man climbing the dark stairs of a medieval tower assures himself by the changing sights glimpsed through its narrow windows that he is getting somewhere after all. </item>
        <item> Art is a fruit that grows in man, like a fruit on a plant, or a child in its mother s womb. </item>
        <item> Pictures and shapes are but secondary objects and please or displease only in the memory. </item>
        <item> The primary distinction of the artist is that he must actively cultivate that state which most men, necessarily, must avoid: the state of being alone. </item>
        <item> All art is a kind of confession, more or less oblique. All artists, if they are to survive, are forced, at last, to tell the whole story; to vomit the anguish up. </item>
        <item> The man who can but sketch his purpose beforehand in words is regarded as a wonder, and every artist and writer possesses that faculty. But gestation, fruition, the laborious rearing of the offspring, putting it to bed every night full fed with milk, embracing it anew every morning with the inexhaustible affection of a mother s heart, licking it clean, dressing it a hundred times in the richest garb only to be instantly destroyed; then never to be cast down at the convulsions of this headlong life till the living masterpiece is perfected which in sculpture speaks to every eye, in literature to every intellect, in painting to every memory, in music to every heart! --this is the task of execution. The hand must be ready at every moment to work in obedience to the mind. </item>
        <item> If we could but paint with the hand what we see with the eye. </item>
        <item> The first mistake of Art is to assume that it s serious. </item>
        <item> Every great work of art has two faces, one toward its own time and one toward the future, toward eternity. </item>
        <item> The essence of all art is to have pleasure in giving pleasure </item>
        <item> Art distills sensations and embodies it with enhanced meaning. </item>
        <item> A frenzied passion for art is a canker that devours everything else. </item>
        <item> The more a man cultivates the arts the less he fornicates. A more and more apparent cleavage occurs between the spirit and the brute. </item>
        <item> In order for the artist to have a world to express he must first be situated in this world, oppressed or oppressing, resigned or rebellious, a man among men. </item>
        <item> Every artist dips his brush in his own soul, and paints his own nature into his pictures. </item>
        <item> Art! Who comprehends her? With whom can one consult concerning this great goddess? </item>
        <item> No one should drive a hard bargain with an artist. </item>
        <item> As for types like my own, obscurely motivated by the conviction that our existence was worthless if we didn t make a turning point of it, we were assigned to the humanities, to poetry, philosophy, painting -- the nursery games of humankind, which had to be left behind when the age of science began. The humanities would be called upon to choose a wallpaper for the crypt, as the end drew near. </item>
        <item> Any artist should be grateful for a na?ve grace which puts him beyond the need to reason elaborately. </item>
        <item> The greater the decrease in the social significance of an art form, the sharper the distinction between criticism and enjoyment by the public. The conventional is uncritically enjoyed, and the truly new is criticized with aversion. </item>
        <item> The strange power of art is sometimes it can show that what people have in common is more urgent than what differentiates them. It seems to me it s something that theatre can do, but it s rare; it s very rare. </item>
        <!--ATTITUDE-->
        <item>Do not judge by appearances; a rich heart may be under a poor coat.</item>
        <item> Good nature is more agreeable in conversation than wit and gives a certain air to the countenance which is more amiable than beauty. </item>
        <item> Sometimes Im so sweet even I cant stand it. </item>
        <item> I got a simple rule about everybody. If you dont treat me right -- shame on you! </item>
        <item> Life would be a perpetual flea hunt if a man were obliged to run down all the innuendoes, inveracities, and insinuations and misrepresentations which are uttered against him. </item>
        <item> We are constantly being surprised that people did things well before we were born. We are constantly remarking on the fact that things are done well by people other than ourselves. The Japanese are a remarkable little people, we say, as if we were doing them a favor. He is an Arab, but you ought to hear him play the zither. Why but? </item>
        <item> While we are focusing on fear, worry, or hate, it is not possible for us to be experiencing happiness, enthusiasm or love. </item>
        <item> There are no menial jobs, only menial attitudes. </item>
        <item> Whenever youre in conflict with someone, there is one factor that can make the difference between damaging your relationship and deepening it. That factor is attitude. </item>
        <item> Id rather be a could-be if I cannot be an are;because a could-be is a maybe who is reaching for a star.Id rather be a has-been than a might-have-been, by far;for a might have-been has never been, but a has was once an are. </item>
        <item> Life is 10 percent what you make it and 90 percent how you take it. </item>
        <item> It is better to know nothing than to know what aint so. </item>
        <item> Our attitudes control our lives. Attitudes are a secret power working twenty-four hours a day, for good or bad. It is of paramount importance that we know how to harness and control this great force. </item>
        <item> Feeling without judgement is a washy draught indeed; but judgement untempered by feeling is too bitter and husky a morsel for human deglutition. </item>
        <item> I never expect to lose. Even when Im the underdog, I still prepare a victory speech. </item>
        <item> You are more likely to act yourself into feelings, than feel yourself into action. </item>
        <item> I dont wait for moods. You accomplish nothing if you do that. Your mind must know it has got to get down to earth. </item>
        <item> There are two big forces at work, external and internal. We have very little control over external forces such as tornadoes, earthquakes, floods, disasters, illness and pain. What really matters is the internal force. How do I respond to those disasters? Over that I have complete control. </item>
        <item> Attitudes are the forerunners of conditions. </item>
        <item> I would rather be first in a little Iberian village than second in Rome. </item>
        <item> In the depths of winter I finally learned there was in me an invincible summer. </item>
        <item> In War: Resolution. In Defeat: Defiance. In Victory: Magnanimity. In Peace: Goodwill. </item>
        <item> If you wish to travel far and fast, travel light. Take off all your envies, jealousies, unforgiveness, selfishness and fears. </item>
        <item> You got to sing like you dont need the money; Love like youll never get hurt; You got to dance like nobodys watchin; Its gotta come from the heart if you want it to work. </item>
        <item> Its not the situation. Its your reaction to the situation. </item>
        <item>Life at any time can become difficult: life at any time can become easy. It all depends upon how one adjusts oneself to life. </item>
        <item>It is not the position, but the disposition. </item>
        <item>The conduct of men depends upon the temperament, not upon a bunch of musty maxims. </item>
        <item>A man can believe a considerable deal of rubbish, and yet go about his daily work in a rational and cheerful manner. </item>
        <item>To different minds, the same world is a hell, and a heaven. </item>
        <item>Its not what happens to you, but how you react to it that matters. </item>
        <item>Win as if you were used to it, lose as if you enjoyed it for a change. </item>
        <item>Events will take their course, it is no good of being angry at them; he is happiest who wisely turns them to the best account. </item>
        <item>If you can react the same way to winning and losing, thats a big accomplishment. That quality is important because it stays with you the rest of your life, and theres going to be a life after tennis thats a lot longer than your tennis life. </item>
        <item>Its how you deal with failure that determines how you achieve success. </item>
        <item>Our attitude towards what has happened to us in life is the important thing to recognize. Once hopeless, my life is now hope-full, but it did not happen overnight. The last of human freedoms, to choose ones attitude in any given set of circumstances, is to choose ones own way. </item>
        <item>A positive attitude can really make dreams come true -- it did for me. </item>
        <item>Zeal is a volcano, the peak of which the grass of indecisiveness does not grow. </item>
        <item>The tears that you spill, the sorrowful, are sweeter than the laughter of snobs and the guffaws of scoffers. </item>
        <item>Nothing in life is so hard that you cant make it easier by the way you take it. </item>
        <item>What happens is not as important as how you react to what happens. </item>
        <item>Lets not be narrow, nasty, and negative. </item>
        <item>People Some people are like wheelbarrows; useful only when pushed, and very easily upset. The time to stop talking is when the other person nods his head affirmatively but says nothing. </item>
        <item>Each experience through which we pass operates ultimately for our good. This is a correct attitude to adopt and we must be able to see it in that light. </item>
        <item>Ability is what youre capable of doing. Motivation determines what you do. Attitude determines how well you do it. </item>
        <item>Life is ten percent what happens to you and ninety percent how you respond to it. </item>
        <item>Its not the load that breaks you down, its the way you carry it. </item>
        <item>We awaken in others the same attitude of mind we hold toward them. </item>
        <item>Those who believe that they are exclusively in the right are generally those who achieve something. </item>
        <item>An inexhaustible good nature is one of the most precious gifts of heaven, spreading itself like oil over the troubled sea of thought, and keeping the mind smooth and equable in the roughest weather. </item>
        <item>Human beings, by changing the inner attitudes of their minds, can change the outer aspects of their lives.</item>
        <item>The greatest discovery of my generation is that human beings can alter their lives by altering their attitudes of mind.</item>
        <item>It is our attitude at the beginning of a difficult task which, more than anything else, will affect its successful outcome.</item>
        <item>Nothing can stop the man with the right mental attitude from achieving his goal; nothing on earth can help the man with the wrong mental attitude.</item>
        <item>Success or failure depends more upon attitude than upon capacity successful men act as though they have accomplished or are enjoying something. Soon it becomes a reality. Act, look, feel successful, conduct yourself accordingly, and you will be amazed at the positive results.</item>
        <item>My attitude is never to be satisfied, never enough, never.</item>
        <item>Up to a point a mans life is shaped by environment, heredity, and the movements and changes in the world around him. Then there comes a time when it lies within his grasp to shape the clay of his life into the sort of thing he wishes to be. Only the weak blame parents, their race, their times, lack of good fortune, or the quirks of fate. Everyone has it within his power to say, This I am today; that I will be tomorrow. The wish, however, must be implemented by deeds.</item>
        <item>A pessimist and an optimist, so much the worse; so much the better.</item>
        <item>Dont introduce me to that man! I want to go on hating him, and I cant hate a man whom I know.</item>
        <item>Two men look out the same prison bars; one sees mud and the other stars.</item>
        <item>In the final analysis there is no other solution to mans progress but the days honest work, the days honest decision, the days generous utterances, and the days good deed.</item>
        <item>Keep your heart right, even when it is sorely wounded.</item>
        <item>We would accomplish many more things if we did not think of them as impossible.</item>
        <item>We are injured and hurt emotionally, Not so much by other people or what they say and dont say, But by our own attitude and our own response.</item>
        <item>Take the attitude of a student, Never be to big to ask questions, Never know to much to learn something new.</item>
        <item>What happens to a man is less significant than what happens within him.</item>
        <item>Could we change our attitude, we should not only see life differently, but life itself would come to be different. Life would undergo a change of appearance because we ourselves had undergone a change of attitude.</item>
        <item>A will finds a way.</item>
        <item>Morale is the state of mind. It is steadfastness and courage and hope. It is confidence and zeal and loyalty. It is elan, esprit de corps and determination.</item>
        <item>Attitudes are more important than facts.</item>
        <item>Ones destination is never a place, but rather a new way of looking at things.</item>
        <item>Your living is determined not so much by what life brings to you as by the attitude you bring to life; not so much by what happens to you as by the way your mind looks at what happens.</item>
        <item>If you will call your troubles experiences, and remember that every experience develops some latent force within you, you will grow vigorous and happy, however adverse your circumstances may seem to be.</item>
        <item>Our attitude toward life determines lifes attitude towards us.</item>
        <item>A great attitude does much more than turn on the lights in our worlds; it seems to magically connect us to all sorts of serendipitous opportunities that were somehow absent before the change.</item>
        <item>Any fact facing us is not as important as our attitude toward it, for that determines our success or failure. The way you think about a fact may defeat you before you ever do anything about it. You are overcome by the fact because you think you are.</item>
        <item>Never elated when someones oppressed, never dejected when another ones blessed.</item>
        <item>Always keep that happy attitude. Pretend that you are holding a beautiful fragrant bouquet.</item>
        <item>There are, it has been said, two types of people in the world. There are those who, when presented with a glass that is exactly half-full, say: this glass is half full. And then there are those who say: this glass is half-empty. The world belongs, however, to those who can look at the glass and say: Whats up with this glass? Excuse me? Excuse me? This is my glass? I dont think so. My glass was full! And it was a bigger glass!</item>
        <item>You play the hand youre dealt. I think the games worthwhile.</item>
        <item>Great effort springs naturally from a great attitude.</item>
        <item>If you have a positive attitude and constantly strive to give your best effort, eventually you will overcome your immediate problems and find you are ready for greater challenges.</item>
        <item>We have unprecedented conditions to deal with and novel adjustments to make -- there can be no doubt of that. We also have a great stock of scientific knowledge unknown to our grandfathers with which to operate. So novel are the conditions, so copious the knowledge, that we must undertake the arduous task of reconsidering a great part of the opinions about man and his relations to his fellow men which have been handed down to us by previous generations who lived in far other conditions and possessed far less information about the world and themselves. We have, however, first to create an unprecedented attitude of mind to cope with unprecedented conditions, and to utilize unprecedented knowledge.</item>
        <item>Ive always believed that you can think positive just as well as you can think negative.</item>
        <item>Its easy to let life deteriorate into making a living instead of making a life. Its not the hours you put in, but what you out into the hours that count. Learn to express rather than impress. Expressing evokes a me too attitude while impressing evokes a so what attitude.</item>
        <item>Attitude is your acceptance of the natural laws, or your rejection of the natural laws.</item>
        <item>There are only 3 colors, 10 digits, and 7 notes; its what we do with them thats important.</item>
        <item>There are times when you just get down, you feel like nobody likes you. Were in high school forever. Its just what we do with it.</item>
        <item>An optimist may see a light where there is none, but why must the pessimist always run to blow it out?</item>
        <item>Dont be against things so much as for things.</item>
        <item>Dont spend time beating on a wall, hoping to transform it into a door.</item>
        <item>An attitude to life which seeks fulfillment in the single-minded pursuit of wealth -- in short, materialism -- does not fit into this world, because it contains within itself no limiting principle, while the environment in which it is placed is strictly limited.</item>
        <item>Eagles come in all shapes and sizes, but you will recognize them chiefly by their attitudes.</item>
        <item>Adopting the right attitude can convert a negative stress into a positive one.</item>
        <item>This is the precept by which I have lived: Prepare for the worst; expect the best; and take what comes.</item>
        <item>They say you cant do it, but sometimes it doesnt always work.</item>
        <item>She would rather light candles than curse the darkness and her glow has warmed the world.</item>
        <item>There is little difference in people, but that little difference makes a big difference. That little difference is attitude. The big difference is whether it is positive or negative.</item>
        <item>Every exit is an entry somewhere.</item>
        <item>The longer I live, the more I realize the impact of attitude on life. Attitude, to me, is more important than facts. It is more important than the past, the education, the money, than circumstances, than failure, than successes, than what other people think or say or do. It is more important than appearance, giftedness or skill. It will make or break a company... a church... a home. The remarkable thing is we have a choice everyday regarding the attitude we will embrace for that day. We cannot change our past... we cannot change the fact that people will act in a certain way. We cannot change the inevitable. The only thing we can do is play on the one string we have, and that is our attitude. I am convinced that life is 10% what happens to me and 90% of how I react to it. And so it is with you... we are in charge of our Attitudes.</item>
        <item>I believe the single most significant decision I can make on a day-to-day basis is my choice of attitude. It is more important than my past, my education, my bankroll, my successes or failures, fame or pain, what other people think of me or say about me, my circumstances, or my position. Attitude keeps me going or cripples my progress. It alone fuels my fire or assaults my hope. When my attitudes are right, there is no barrier too high, no valley too deep, no dream too extreme, no challenge too great for me.</item>
        <item>Words can never adequately convey the incredible impact of our attitudes toward life. The longer I live the more convinced I become that life is 10 percent what happens to us and 90 percent how we respond to it.</item>
        <item>If you cant change your fate, change your attitude.</item>
        <item>The world is a looking glass and gives back to every man the reflection of his own face.</item>
        <item>It started when I left Vegas that first time, skipping the hotel bill, driving off in that red convertible all alone, drunk and crazy, back to L.A. Thats exactly what I felt. Fear and loathing.</item>
        <item>He was always leaning forward, pushing something invisible ahead of him.</item>
        <item>We lost because we told ourselves we lost.</item>
        <item>Develop an attitude of gratitude, and give thanks for everything that happens to you, knowing that every step forward is a step toward achieving something bigger and better than your current situation.</item>
        <item>Whenever a fellow tells me he is bipartisan, I know hes going to vote against me.</item>
        <item>Ive never run into a guy who could win at the top level in anything today and didnt have the right attitude, didnt give it everything he had, at least while he was doing it; wasnt prepared and didnt have the whole program worked out.</item>
        <item>Take everything easy and quit dreaming and brooding and you will be well guarded from a thousand evils.</item>
        <item>Two-minute attitude drill: To everyone: You can trust me. Im committed to excellence. I care about you as a person. EVERY DAY: Do good. Do your best. Treat others as you would be treated. FOR TODAY: Nothing negative will escape my lips.</item>
        <item>Whether a glass is half full or half empty depends on the attitude of the person looking at it.</item>
        <item>The most vital thing in a mans life is his mental attitude.</item>
        <item>Optimism is the cheerful frame of mind that enables a teakettle to sing, though in hot water up to its nose.</item>
        <item>One man gets nothing but discord out of a piano; another gets harmony. No one claims the piano is at fault. Life is about the same. The discord is there, and the harmony is there. Study to play it correctly, and it will give forth the beauty; play it falsely, and it will give forth the ugliness. Life is not at fault.</item>
        <item>Nothing else is needed to make you depressed, than to fancy you are so.</item>
        <item>Irritation in the heart of a believer is always an invitation to the devil to stand by.</item>
        <item>If you look for the positive things in life; you will find them.</item>
        <item>Your attitude determines your altitude.</item>
        <item>A healthy attitude is contagious but dont wait to catch it from others. Be a carrier.</item>
        <item>Attitude is a little thing that makes a big difference.</item>
        <item>Growl all day and youll feel dog tired all night.</item>
        <item>I am an optimist, unrepentant and militant. After all, in order not to be a fool an optimist must know how sad a place the world can be. It is only the pessimist who finds this out anew every day.</item>
        <item>Our judgments judge us; and nothing reveals us or exposes our weaknesses more ingeniously than the attitude of pronouncing upon our fellows. </item>
        <item>Life is the movie you see through your own eyes. It makes little difference whats happening out there. Its how you take it that counts. </item>
        <item>There are things I cant force. I must adjust. There are times when the greatest change needed is a change of my viewpoint. </item>
        <item>Generalists, people with moderately strong attachments to many ideas, should be hard to interrupt, and once interrupted, should have weaker, shorter negative reactions since they have alternative paths to realize their plans. Specialists, people with stronger attachments to fewer ideas, should be easier to interrupt, and once interrupted, should have stronger, more sustained negative reactions because they have fewer alternative pathways to realize their plans. Generalists should be the upbeat, positive people in the profession while specialists should be their grouchy, negative counterparts. </item>
        <item>Some men have thousands of reasons why they cannot do what they want to, when all they need is one reason why they can. </item>
        <item>One ship drives east and other drives west by the same winds that blow. Its the set of the sails and not the gales that determines the way they go. </item>
        <item>Seriousness is the only refuge of the shallow. </item>
        <item>The cynic knows the price of everything and the value of nothing. </item>
        <item>Between the optimist and the pessimist, the difference is droll. The optimist sees the doughnut; the pessimist the hole! </item>
        <item>You can complain because roses have thorns, or you can rejoice because thorns have roses. </item>
        <item>Nothing will work unless you do. </item>
        <item>You cannot tailor make your situation in life, but you can tailor make your attitudes to fit those situations. </item>
        <item>You cannot climb the ladder of success dressed in the costume of failure. </item>
        <item>Positive thinking will let you do everything better than negative thinking will. </item>
        <!--BEAUTY-->
        <item>A poor beauty finds more lovers than husbands. </item>
        <item>Beauty, unaccompanied by virtue, is as a flower without perfume. </item>
        <item>The loveliest faces are to be seen by moonlight, when one sees half with the eye and half with the fancy. </item>
        <item>Beauty is a good letter of introduction. </item>
        <item>There is nothing that makes its way more directly to the soul than beauty. </item>
        <item>Let there be nothing within thee that is not very beautiful and very gentle, and there will be nothing without thee that is not beautiful and softened by the spell of thy presence. </item>
        <item>Then he felt quite ashamed, and hid his head under his wing; for he did not know what to do, he was so happy, and yet not at all proud. He had been persecuted and despised for his ugliness, and now he heard them say he was the most beautiful of all the birds. Even the elder-tree bent down its bows into the water before him, and the sun shone warm and bright. He would never became vain or conceited, and would always remembered how it felt to be despised and teased, and he was very sorry for all the creatures who are so treated merely because they are different from those around them. Then he rustled his feathers, curved his slender neck, and cried joyfully, from the depths of his heart, </item>
        <item>What ever beauty may be, it has for its basis order, and for its essence unity. </item>
        <item>Beauty is one of the rare things that do not lead to doubt of God. </item>
        <item>Things are beautiful if you love them. </item>
        <item>Beauty is one of the rare things that do not lead to doubt of God. </item>
        <item>Personal beauty is a greater recommendation than any letter of reference. </item>
        <item>Beauty depends on size as well as symmetry. No very small animal can be beautiful, for looking at it takes so small a portion of time that the impression of it will be confused. Nor can any very large one, for a whole view of it cannot be had at once, and so there will be no unity and completeness. </item>
        <item>Strange that the vanity which accompanies beauty --excusable, perhaps, when there is such great beauty, or at any rate understandable --should persist after the beauty was gone. </item>
        <item>The best part of beauty is that which no picture can express. </item>
        <item>There is no excellent beauty that hath not some strangeness in the proportion. </item>
        <item>Beauty is but the sensible image of the Infinite. Like truth and justice it lives within us; like virtue and the moral law it is a companion of the soul. </item>
        <item>Beauty itself is but the sensible image of the infinite. </item>
        <item>Im not ugly, but my beauty is a total creation. </item>
        <item>Beauty is desired in order that it may be befouled; not for its own sake, but for the joy brought by the certainty of profaning it. </item>
        <item>All forms of beauty, like all possible phenomena, contain an element of the eternal and an element of the transitory -- of the absolute and of the particular. Absolute and eternal beauty does not exist, or rather it is only an abstraction creamed from the general surface of different beauties. The particular element in each manifestation comes from the emotions: and just as we have our own particular emotions, so we have our own beauty. </item>
        <item>There are as many kinds of beauty as there are habitual ways of seeking happiness. </item>
        <item>The loveliest face in all the world will not please you if you see it suddenly eye to eye, at a distance of half an inch from your own. </item>
        <item>The idea that happiness could have a share in beauty would be too much of a good thing. </item>
        <item>Beauty is in the heart of the beholder. </item>
        <!--BELIEFE 24 -->
        <item>For those who believe, no proof is necessary. For those who dont believe, no proof is possible.</item>
        <item>sickness is a thing of the spirit</item>
        <item>A sign inside the front door of Holy Cross Primary School, in north Belfast, reads: If wed been born where they were born and taught what they were taught, we would believe what they believe.</item>
        <item>I believe in the sun even if it isnt shining. I believe in love even when I am alone. I believe in God even when He is silent.</item>
        <item>To believe a thing is impossible is to make it so.</item>
        <item>And if we now cast our eyes over the nations of the earth, we shall find that, instead of possessing the pure religion of the Gospel, they may be divided either into infidels, who deny the truth; or politicians who make religion a stalking horse for their ambition; or professors, who walk in the trammels of orthodoxy, and are more attentive to traditions and ordinances of men than to the oracles of truth.</item>
        <item>The will to do springs from the knowledge that we can do.</item>
        <item>Our systems, perhaps, are nothing more than an unconscious apology for our faults --a gigantic scaffolding whose object is to hide from us our favorite sin.</item>
        <item>It doesnt matter how many say it cannot be done or how many people have tried it before; its important to realize that whatever youre doing, its your first attempt at it.</item>
        <item>I believe we are still so innocent. The species are still so innocent that a person who is apt to be murdered believes that the murderer, just before he puts the final wrench on his throat, will have enough compassion to give him one sweet cup of water.</item>
        <item>If you dont change your beliefs, your life will be like this forever. Is that good news?</item>
        <item>Light half-believers of our casual creeds, who never deeply felt, nor clearly will d, whose insight never has borne fruit in deeds, whose vague resolves never have been fulfilled.</item>
        <item>Sooner or later, those who win are those who think they can.</item>
        <item>Strong beliefs win strong men, and then make them stronger.</item>
        <item>I started out by believing God for a newer car than the one I was driving. I started out believing God for a nicer apartment than I had. Then I moved up.</item>
        <item>Confronted with the impossibility of remaining faithful to ones beliefs, and the equal impossibility of becoming free of them, one can be driven to the most inhuman excesses.</item>
        <item>We have all had the experience of finding that our reactions and perhaps even our deeds have denied beliefs we thought were ours.</item>
        <item>Those who say it cant be done are usually interrupted by others doing it.</item>
        <item>More persons, on the whole, are humbugged by believing in nothing than by believing in too much.</item>
        <item>Every time a child says, I dont believe in fairies, there is a fairy somewhere that falls down dead.</item>
        <item>Once you begin to believe there is help out there, you will know it to be true.</item>
        <item>The essential element in personal magnetism is a consuming sincerity -- an overwhelming faith in the importance of the work one has to do.</item>
        <item>When you think of the huge uninterrupted success of a book like Don Quixote, youre bound to realize that if humankind have not yet finished being revenged, by sheer laughter, for being let down in their greatest hope, it is because that hope was cherished so long and lay so deep!</item>
        <item>Everything is possible for him who believes.</item>
        <!--BIBLE 10-->
        <item>Men may not read the gospel in sealskin, or the gospel in morocco, or the gospel in cloth covers, but they cant get away from the gospel in shoe leather.</item>
        <item>The real truth is that while He came to preach the gospel, His chief object in coming was that there might be a gospel to preach.</item>
        <item>One of my less pleasant chores when I was young was to read the Bible from one end to the other. Reading the Bible straight through is at least 70 percent discipline, like learning Latin. But the good parts are, of course, simply amazing. God is an extremely uneven writer, but when Hes good, nobody can touch Him.</item>
        <item>If they had a social gospel in the days of the prodigal son, somebody would have given him a bed and a sandwich and he never would have gone home.</item>
        <item>It is Christ Himself, not the Bible, who is the true word of God. The Bible, read in the right spirit and with the guidance of good teachers, will bring us to Him. We must not use the Bible as a sort of encyclopedia out of which texts can be taken for use as weapons.</item>
        <item>The glory of the gospel is that when the church is absolutely different from the world, she invariably attracts it.</item>
        <item>The gospel to me is simply irresistible.</item>
        <item>The gospel is neither a discussion or a debate. It is an announcement.</item>
        <item>Each generation of the church in each setting has the responsibility of communicating the gospel in understandable terms, considering the language and thought-forms of that setting.</item>
        <item>Philosophical argument has sometimes shaken my reason for the faith that was in me; but my heart has always assured me that the Gospel of Jesus Christ must be reality.</item>
        <!--BOOKS 25-->
        <item>Books are the legacies that a great genius leaves to mankind, which are delivered down from generation to generation as presents to the posterity of those who are yet unborn.</item>
        <item>Books that have become classics -- books that have had their day and now get more praise than perusal -- always remind me of retired colonels and majors and captains who, having reached the age limit, find themselves retired on half pay.</item>
        <item>Literature is made upon any occasion that a challenge is put to the legal apparatus by conscience in touch with humanity.</item>
        <item>The writer in western civilization has become not a voice of his tribe, but of his individuality. This is a very narrow-minded situation.</item>
        <item>If the most significant characteristic of man is the complex of biological needs he shares with all members of his species, then the best lives for the writer to observe are those in which the role of natural necessity is clearest, namely, the lives of the very poor.</item>
        <item>Literary imagination is an aesthetic object offered by a writer to a lover of books.</item>
        <item>Literature is without proofs. By which it must be understood that it cannot prove, not only what it says, but even that it is worth the trouble of saying it.</item>
        <item>In the present age, alas! our pens are ravished by unlettered authors and unmannered critics, that make a havoc rather than a building, a wilderness rather than a garden. But, a lack! what boots it to drop tears upon the preterit?</item>
        <item>Do not worry about the incarnation of ideas. If you are a poet, your works will contain them without your knowledge -- they will be both moral and national if you follow your inspiration freely.</item>
        <item>Child! Do not throw this book about Refrain from the unholy pleasureOf cutting all the pictures out!Preserve it as your chiefest treasure.</item>
        <item>The naturalistic literature of this country has reached such a state that no family of characters is considered true to life which does not include at least two hypochondriacs, one sadist, and one old man who spills food down the front of his vest.</item>
        <item>The book borrower...proves himself to be an inveterate collector of books not so much by the fervor with which he guards his borrowed treasures...as by his failure to read these books.</item>
        <item>Definition of a classic: a book everyone is assumed to have read and often thinks they have.</item>
        <item>The great standard of literature as to purity and exactness of style is the Bible.</item>
        <item>There are certain books in the world which every searcher for truth must know: the Bible, the Critique of Pure Reason, the Origin of Species, and Karl Marxs Capital.</item>
        <item>Literature is not exhaustible, for the sufficient and simple reason that a single book is not. A book is not an isolated entity: it is a narration, an axis of innumerable narrations. One literature differs from another, either before or after it, not so much because of the text as for the manner in which it is read.</item>
        <item>A losing trade, I assure you, sir: literature is a drug.</item>
        <item>No one is fit to judge a book until he has rounded Cape Horn in a sailing vessel, until he has bumped into two or three icebergs, until he has been lost in the sands of the desert, until he has spent a few years in the House of the Dead.</item>
        <item>All literature is political.</item>
        <item>English literature is a kind of training in social ethics. English trains you to handle a body of information in a way that is conducive to action.</item>
        <item>The struggle of literature is in fact a struggle to escape from the confines of language; it stretches out from the utmost limits of what can be said; what stirs literature is the call and attraction of what is not in the dictionary.</item>
        <item>When politicians and politically minded people pay too much attention to literature, it is a bad sign -- a bad sign mostly for literature. But it is also a bad sign when they dont want to hear the word mentioned.</item>
        <item>A classic is a book that has never finished saying what it has to say.</item>
        <item>There is a great discovery still to be made in literature, that of paying literary men by the quantity they do not write.</item>
        <item>Alice was beginning to get very tired of sitting by her sister on the bank, and of having nothing to do: once or twice she had peeped into the book her sister was reading, but it had no pictures or conversations in it, and what is the use of a book thought Alice, without pictures or conversations?</item>
        <!--BRAVE25-->
        <item>Some have been thought brave because they didnt have the courage to run away.</item>
        <item>Courage and perseverance have a magical talisman, before which difficulties disappear and obstacles vanish into air.</item>
        <item>Courage that grows from constitution often forsakes a man when he has occasion for it; courage which arises from a sense of duty acts ;in a uniform manner.</item>
        <item>There is another side to chivalry. If it dispenses leniency, it may with equal justification invoke control.</item>
        <item>It is easy to be brave from a safe distance.</item>
        <item>As a rock on the seashore he standeth firm, and the dashing of the waves disturbeth him not. He raiseth his head like a tower on a hill, and the arrows of fortune drop at his feet. In the instant of danger, the courage of his heart here, and scorn to fly.</item>
        <item>Often the test of courage is not to die but to live.</item>
        <item>Whether you be man or woman you will never do anything in this world without courage. It is the greatest quality of the mind next to honor.</item>
        <item>It takes a certain courage and a certain greatness to be truly base.</item>
        <item>Until the day of his death, no man can be sure of his courage.</item>
        <item>The ideal man bears the accidents of life with dignity and grace, making the best of circumstances.</item>
        <item>It is easy to fly into a passion... anybody can do that, but to be angry with the right person to the right extent and at the right time and in the right way that is not easy.</item>
        <item>The beauty of the soul shines out when a man bears with composure one heavy mischance after another, not because he does not feel them, but because he is a man of high and heroic temper.</item>
        <item>Boldness is ever blind, for it sees not dangers and inconveniences whence it is bad in council though good in execution.</item>
        <item>The brave man is not he who feels no fear, For that were stupid and irrational; But he, whose noble soul its fears subdues, And bravely dares the danger nature shrinks from.</item>
        <item>Nothing splendid has ever been achieved except by those who dared believe that something inside them was superior to circumstance.</item>
        <item>The scars you acquire while exercising courage will never make you feel inferior.</item>
        <item>Be daring, be different, be impractical, be anything that will assert integrity of purpose and imaginative vision against the play-it-safers, the creatures of the commonplace, the slaves of the ordinary.</item>
        <item>Courage is a special kind of knowledge: the knowledge of how to fear what ought to be feared and how not to fear what ought no to be feared.</item>
        <item>It is the perpetual dread of fear, the fear of fear, that shapes the face of a brave man.</item>
        <item>Courage is fear that has said its prayers.</item>
        <item>If we have the courage and tenacity of our forebears, who stood firmly like a rock against the lash of slavery, we shall find a way to do for our day what they did for theirs.</item>
        <item>Do not fear, for those who are with us, are more than those who are with them. 2 Kings 6:16</item>
        <item>Finally, be strong in the Lord, and in the strength of His might. Ephesians 6:10</item>
        <item>I can do all things through him who strengthens me. Philippians 4:13</item>
        <item>Dont open a shop unless you like to smile.</item>
        <!--BUSINESS-->
        <item>The go-between wears out a thousand sandals.</item>
        <item>Instead of focusing on their individual agendas, collaborative partnerships establish common goals. In order to address problems that lie beyond any single agencys exclusive purview, but which concern them all, partners agree to pool resources, jointly plan, implement, and evaluate new services and procedures, and delegate individual responsibility for the outcomes of their joint efforts.</item>
        <item>Buying is cheaper than asking.</item>
        <item>Work is our business; its success is God s.</item>
        <item>A miser and a liar bargain quickly.</item>
        <item>When two friends have a common bank account, one sings and the other weeps.</item>
        <item>Cut your losses and let your profits run.</item>
        <item>In business partnerships and marriage partnerships, oh, the cheating that goes on.</item>
        <item>It is the privilege of posterity to set matters right between those antagonists who, by their rivalry for greatness, divided a whole age.</item>
        <item>There is nothing more requisite in business than dispatch.</item>
        <item>The one sure way to conciliate a tiger is to allow oneself to be devoured.</item>
        <item>The basic rule of free enterprise: You must give in order to get.</item>
        <item>Treat employees like partners, and they act like partners.</item>
        <item>Anybody can cut prices, but it takes brains to produce a better article.</item>
        <item>Frankly, I dont want to see a rapid upturn. I want it to hold until some of these idiotic competitors go bust.</item>
        <item>Nobody ever lost money taking a profit.</item>
        <item>Forty for you, sixty for me And equal partners we will be</item>
        <item>I work in a strange business, and trust is a word thats not even in the vocabulary.</item>
        <item>If you wish to prosper, let your customer prosper.When people have learned this lesson, everyone will seek his individual welfare in the general welfare. Then jealousies between man and man, city and city, province and province, nation and nation, will no longer trouble the world.</item>
        <item>The fellow who says hell meet you halfway usually thinks hes standing on the dividing line.</item>
        <item>For the merchant, even honesty is a financial speculation.</item>
        <item>Executives are like joggers. If you stop a jogger, he goes on running on the spot. If you drag an executive away from his business, he goes on running on the spot, pawing the ground, talking business. He never stops hurtling onwards, making decisions and executing them.</item>
        <item>No sale is really complete until the product is worn out, and the customer is satisfied.</item>
        <item>Business is more exciting than any game.</item>
       <!--CATS 24-->
        <item>In a cats eye, all things belong to cats.</item>
        <item>One of the problems of taking things apart and seeing how they work - supposing youre trying to find out how a cat works--you take that cat apart to see how it works, what youve got in your hands is a non-working cat. The cat wasnt a sort of clunky mechanism that was susceptible to our available tools of analysis.</item>
        <item>Cruel, but composed and bland Dumb, inscrutable and grand,So Tiberius might have sat Had Tiberius been a cat.</item>
        <item>Both ardent lovers and austere scholars, when once they come to the years of discretion, love cats, so strong and gentle, the pride of the household, who like them are sensitive to the cold, and sedentary.</item>
        <item>A lion, for instance, which in nature is not a very distinctive object, was portrayed, for greater distinction, with its leonine attributes, its fierce expression, frightful claws, lithe and ,lissom body all vastly exaggerated, so that indeed it looked more like a lion than did ever any lion of nature. In this wise, by turning away from true representation and adopting a character all its own, was the heraldic lion born, and with it came also the manner of depictin all the other beasts and forms and patterns which is so peculiarly heraldic.</item>
        <item>If a cat spoke, it would say things like Hey, I dont see the problem here.</item>
        <item>Dogs come when they are called; cats take a message and get back to you.</item>
        <item>One small cat changes coming home to an empty house to coming home.</item>
        <item>Cats dont like change without their consent.</item>
        <item>Cats can be cooperative when something feels good, which, to a cat, is the way everything is supposed to feel as much of the time as possible.</item>
        <item>It is a very inconvenient habit of kittens (Alice had once made the remark) that whatever you say to them, they always purr.</item>
        <item>I said something which gave you to think I hated cats. But gad, sir, I am one of the most fanatical cat lovers in the business. If you hate them, I may learn to hate you. If your allergies hate them, I will tolerate the situation to the best of my ability.</item>
        <item>Your rat tail is all the fashion now. I prefer a bushy plume, carried straight up. You are Siamese and your ancestors lived in trees. Mine lived in palaces. It has been suggested to me that I am a bit of a snob. How true! I prefer to be.Raymond Chandler Take a cat, nourish it well with milk And tender meat, make it a couch of silk But let it see a mouse along the wall And it abandones milk and meat and all Chaucer I love my cats because I love my home, and little by little they become its visible soul.</item>
        <item>The appearance of a cat is not controlled by the color of its skin but by the content of its hairacter.</item>
        <item>One cat in a house is a sign of loneliness, two of barrenness, and three of sodomy.</item>
        <item>Authors like cats because they are such quiet, lovable, wise creatures, and cats like authors for the same reasons.</item>
        <item>The smallest feline is a masterpiece.</item>
        <item>Curiosity is the very basis of education and if you tell me that curiosity killed the cat, I say only the cat died nobly.</item>
        <item>Never try to outstubborn a cat.</item>
        <item>If you want to be a psychological novelist and write about human beings, the best thing you can do is keep a pair of cats.</item>
        <item>Cats are intended to teach us that not everything in nature has a function.</item>
        <item>Bragging is not an attractive trait, but lets be honest. A man who catches a big fish doesnt go home through an alley.</item>
        <item>If a fish is the movement of water embodied, given shape, then cat is a diagram and pattern of subtle air.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>